Office of the President Records UA001
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Burton Crosby Hallowell, administrative records and related papers, 1925 -- 2002; 1967 -- 1976; UA001.012; 25.6 Linear Feet; 8 Digital Object(s)
  - Correspondence, 1967 -- 1988; 1967 -- 1976; UA001.012.001; 2.65 Linear Feet
    - Correspondence, 1907 -- 1975; UA001.012.001.005.00007 (Box 5)
    - Correspondence, 1908 -- 1975; UA001.012.001.005.00008 (Box 5)
    - Correspondence, 1909 -- 1975; UA001.012.001.005.00009 (Box 5)
    - Correspondence, 1910 -- 1975; UA001.012.001.005.00010 (Box 5)
    - Correspondence, 1911 -- 1975; UA001.012.001.005.00011 (Box 5)
    - Correspondence, 1912 -- 1975; UA001.012.001.005.00012 (Box 5)
    - Correspondence, Alumni, 1975; UA001.012.001.005.00013 (Box 5)
    - Correspondence, 1901 -- 1976; UA001.012.001.005.00014 (Box 5)
    - Correspondence, 1902 -- 1976; UA001.012.001.005.00015 (Box 5)
    - Correspondence, 1903 -- 1976; UA001.012.001.005.00016 (Box 5)
    - Correspondence, 1904 -- 1976; UA001.012.001.005.00017 (Box 5)
    - Correspondence, 1905 -- 1976; UA001.012.001.005.00018 (Box 5)
    - Correspondence, 1906 -- 1976; UA001.012.001.005.00019 (Box 5)
    - Dental School, 1967; UA001.012.001.006.00001 (Box 6)
    - Dental School, 1968; UA001.012.001.006.00002 (Box 6)
    - Dental School, 1969; UA001.012.001.006.00003 (Box 6)
    - Dental School, 1970; UA001.012.001.006.00004 (Box 6)
    - Dental School, 1971; UA001.012.001.006.00005 (Box 6)
    - Dental School, 1972; UA001.012.001.006.00006 (Box 6)
    - Dental School, 1973; UA001.012.001.006.00007 (Box 6)
    - Dental School, 1974; UA001.012.001.006.00008 (Box 6)
    - Dental School, 1975; UA001.012.001.006.00009 (Box 6)
    - Tufts Dental Alumni Association, 1968; UA001.012.001.006.00010 (Box 6)
    - Dental School and the Forsyth School, 1969; UA001.012.001.006.00011 (Box 6)
    - Dental School: grant application, 1968; UA001.012.001.006.00012 (Box 6)
    - Dental School: grant application, 1973; UA001.012.001.006.00013 (Box 6)
    - Dental School: grant application, 1970; UA001.012.001.006.00014 (Box 6)
    - Dental School, grounds and buildings, and building specifications, 1970; UA001.012.001.006.00015 (Box 6)
    - Dental School, grounds and buildings, and cost estimates, 1972; UA001.012.001.006.00016 (Box 6)
    - Dental School, grounds and buildings, and the Dental Health Sciences Building (general), 1967 -- 1974; UA001.012.001.006.00017 (Box 6)
    - Dental School, grounds and buildings, and the Dental Health Sciences Building, 1968 -- 1973; UA001.012.001.006.00018 (Box 6)
      Box 1 of 4
    - Dental School, grounds and buildings, and the Dental Health Sciences Building, 1970; UA001.012.001.006.00019 (Box 6)
      Box 2 of 4
    - Dental School, grounds and buildings, and the Dental Health Sciences Building, 1970; UA001.012.001.006.00020 (Box 6)
      Box 3 of 4
    - Dental School, grounds and buildings, and the Dental Health Sciences Building, 1971 -- 1973; UA001.012.001.006.00021 (Box 6)
      Box 4 of 4
    - Dental School, grounds and buildings, and financing, 1968 -- 1973; UA001.012.001.006.00022 (Box 6)
    - Dental School: presentation display, 1970; UA001.012.001.006.00023 (Box 6)
    - Dental School: Proposal to Increase Dental Manpower, 1968 -- 1969; UA001.012.001.006.00024 (Box 6)
    - Sheetz, John W. (Administration) (2) [Correspondence from John W. Sheetz, Vice President for Resources, to Burton C. Hallowell and Jean Mayer], 1968 -- 1978; UA001.012.001.055.00001 (Box 55)
      This folder was found uncataloged in stacks. It contains correspondence from Vice President for Resources, John Sheetz, to Burton C. Hallowell and Jean Mayer. There are letters regarding Co-ed dorms, plans for university space and building, budget and salary reviews, wage discrimination, and the elephant head from Franklin Park Zoo.
    - Sheetz, John W. (Administration) (3) [Advance Proof of the 1975 alumni opinion survey], 1968 -- 1978; UA001.012.001.055.00002 (Box 55)
      This folder was found uncataloged in stacks. It contains an advance proof of John W. Sheetz' Report on the Dec. 1975 Opinion Survey. The newspaper publication of this report can by found in UA042.001.019.00002. This reports includes alumni opinions on many hot topics of the time, including homosexuality, co-ed dorms, affirmative action, alumni communications, attitudes re: Tufts, fraternaties/sororities, sex discrimination, admission, faculty. Also includes transcribed quotes from respondants on the topics of ROTC, social attitudes, and fund raising. The results of this survey give a great overview of the opinions of alumni of various age groups in 1975.
  - Articles and speeches, 1965 -- 1976; UA001.012.002; 0.25 Linear Feet
    This subseries consists of articles and speeches authored by Burton C. Hallowell during his presidency (1967-1976). These include addresses given at functions such as Hallowell's inauguration, commencements, conferences, and meetings of associations. The speeches appear in the form of drafts, transcripts, and reprints and greatly outnumber Hallowell's published works. Articles include works written for the Boston Globe and Tufts publications on liberal arts education.
    This subseries is not arranged.
    - Articles and speeches, 1967 -- 1975; UA001.012.002.006.00001 (Box 6)
    - Articles and speeches delivered at honors programs and convocations, 1967 -- 1974; UA001.012.002.006.00002 (Box 6)
    - Articles and speeches, 1967 -- 1976; UA001.012.002.006.00003 (Box 6)
    - Articles and matriculation speeches, 1967 -- 1975; UA001.012.002.006.00004 (Box 6)
    - Articles and speeches delivered off-campus, 1968 -- 1973; UA001.012.002.006.00005 (Box 6)
    - Articles and commencement speeches, 1971 -- 1974; UA001.012.002.006.00006 (Box 6)
  - Clippings, 1967 -- 1975; UA001.012.003; 0.25 Linear Feet
    This subseries consists of newspaper clippings documenting various aspects of Burton C. Hallowell's presidency (1967-1976) at Tufts. Topics represented include Hallowell's inauguration and resignation, the Tufts student body, and student unrest. Many of the clippings have been cut out of newspapers and pasted to sheets of paper.
    - Clippings, 1967 -- 1972; UA001.012.003.007.00001 (Box 7)
    - Clippings, 1967 -- 1973; UA001.012.003.007.00002 (Box 7)
    - Clippings, 1967 -- 1975; UA001.012.003.007.00003 (Box 7)
  - Subject files, 1957 -- 1986; 1967 -- 1976; UA001.012.004; 9.0 Linear Feet
    This subseries consists of subject files containing memoranda, reports, correspondence, clippings, committee records, and related materials documenting the duties and events of the Burton C. Hallowell presidential administration at Tufts University. These files were previously arranged and no attempt has been made to reconstruct original order. Much of the University's committee work of the time is represented in this series, which includes the records of the University Steering Committee (USC), the Committee on Undergraduate Education (CUE), the Presidential Administrative Advisory Group (PAAG), and the Association of Independent Colleges and Universities of Massachusetts (AICUM). The administration of select schools and programs, most notably the Tufts New England Medical Center, is documented. Events, such as a lecture by Senator Edward Kennedy and the "Construction Site Crisis," are also represented.
    This subseries is arranged alphabetically.
    - AICUM, 1967 -- 1968; UA001.012.004.008.00001 (Box 8)
    - AICUM, 1968; UA001.012.004.008.00002 (Box 8)
    - AICUM, 1901 -- 1969; UA001.012.004.008.00003 (Box 8)
    - AICUM, 1907 -- 1969; UA001.012.004.008.00004 (Box 8)
    - AICUM, 1907 -- 1970; UA001.012.004.008.00005 (Box 8)
    - AICUM, 1971; UA001.012.004.008.00006 (Box 8)
    - AICUM, 1971; UA001.012.004.009.00001 (Box 9)
    - AICUM, 1901 -- 1972; UA001.012.004.009.00002 (Box 9)
    - AICUM, 1909 -- 1972; UA001.012.004.009.00003 (Box 9)
    - AICUM, 1911 -- 1972; UA001.012.004.009.00004 (Box 9)
    - AICUM: book, 1972; UA001.012.004.009.00005 (Box 9)
    - AICUM, 1901 -- 1973; UA001.012.004.010.00001 (Box 10)
    - AICUM, 1973; UA001.012.004.010.00002 (Box 10)
    - AICUM, 1973; UA001.012.004.010.00003 (Box 10)
    - AICUM, 1973; UA001.012.004.010.00004 (Box 10)
    - AICUM: minutes, 1972 -- 1973; UA001.012.004.011.00001 (Box 11)
    - AICUM: reports, 1973; UA001.012.004.011.00002 (Box 11)
    - AICUM, 1901 -- 1974; UA001.012.004.011.00003 (Box 11)
    - AICUM, 1904 -- 1974; UA001.012.004.011.00004 (Box 11)
    - AICUM, 1908 -- 1974; UA001.012.004.011.00005 (Box 11)
    - AICUM, 1910 -- 1974; UA001.012.004.011.00006 (Box 11)
    - AICUM, 1910 -- 1974; UA001.012.004.011.00007 (Box 11)
    - AICUM, 1974; UA001.012.004.012.00001 (Box 12)
    - AICUM, 1901 -- 1975; UA001.012.004.012.00002 (Box 12)
    - AICUM, 1903 -- 1975; UA001.012.004.012.00003 (Box 12)
    - AICUM, 1909 -- 1975; UA001.012.004.012.00004 (Box 12)
    - AICUM: Academy for Educational Development, 1973; UA001.012.004.013.00001 (Box 13)
    - AICUM: Forum, 1973 -- 1974; UA001.012.004.013.00002 (Box 13)
    - AICUM: FORUM, 1974 -- 1975; UA001.012.004.013.00003 (Box 13)
    - AICUM: Massachusetts Advisory Council on Education (MACE), 1975; UA001.012.004.013.00004 (Box 13)
    - AICUM: Massachusetts Advisory Council on Education (MACE), 1972 -- 1975; UA001.012.004.013.00005 (Box 13)
    - AICUM: Organization for Social and Technical Innovation (OSTI), 1973; UA001.012.004.013.00006 (Box 13)
    - AICUM: Organization for Social and Technical Innovation (OSTI), 1972 -- 1973; UA001.012.004.013.00007 (Box 13)
    - AICUM: Organization for Social and Technical Innovation (OSTI), 1973; UA001.012.004.013.00008 (Box 13)
    - Alumni Newsletter, 1972 -- 1973; UA001.012.004.013.00009 (Box 13)
    - Bicentennial Committee, 1973 -- 1975; UA001.012.004.014.00001 (Box 14)
    - Biographical materials, 1967 -- 1976; UA001.012.004.014.00002 (Box 14)
    - Class size analysis, 1968; UA001.012.004.014.00003 (Box 14)
    - Community relations, 1964 -- 1972; UA001.012.004.014.00004 (Box 14)
    - Committee on Undergraduate Education (CUE), 1970 -- 1972; UA001.012.004.014.00005 (Box 14)
    - Committee on Undergraduate Education (CUE): charge, 1971 -- 1972; UA001.012.004.014.00006 (Box 14)
    - Committee on Undergraduate Education (CUE): department chair interviews, 1972 -- 1973; UA001.012.004.014.00007 (Box 14)
    - Committee on Undergraduate Education (CUE): Richard Dudman, 1971 -- 1972; UA001.012.004.014.00008 (Box 14)
    - Committee on Undergraduate Education (CUE): engineering, 1971 -- 1972; UA001.012.004.014.00009 (Box 14)
    - Committee on Undergraduate Education (CUE): faculty, 1971 -- 1972; UA001.012.004.014.00010 (Box 14)
    - Committee on Undergraduate Education (CUE): Feinberg - freshman tutorials, 1972; UA001.012.004.014.00011 (Box 14)
    - Committee on Undergraduate Education (CUE): financial aid, 1970 -- 1972; UA001.012.004.014.00012 (Box 14)
    - Committee on Undergraduate Education (CUE): foci, 1972; UA001.012.004.014.00013 (Box 14)
    - Committee on Undergraduate Education (CUE): handouts, 1970 -- 1972; UA001.012.004.014.00014 (Box 14)
    - Committee on Undergraduate Education (CUE): IGI, 1970; UA001.012.004.014.00015 (Box 14)
    - Committee on Undergraduate Education (CUE): members, 1970; UA001.012.004.014.00016 (Box 14)
    - Committee on Undergraduate Education (CUE): memos, 1972 -- 1974; UA001.012.004.014.00017 (Box 14)
    - Committee on Undergraduate Education (CUE): minutes, 1972; UA001.012.004.014.00018 (Box 14)
    - Committee on Undergraduate Education (CUE): postition papers, 1972; UA001.012.004.014.00019 (Box 14)
    - Committee on Undergraduate Education (CUE): priorities, 1972; UA001.012.004.014.00020 (Box 14)
    - Committee on Undergraduate Education (CUE): subcommittees, 1972 -- 1973; UA001.012.004.014.00021 (Box 14)
    - Committee on Undergraduate Education (CUE): Tennant - Frustrations and Hopes, 1972; UA001.012.004.015.00001 (Box 15)
    - Committee on Undergraduate Education (CUE): draft report introduction, 1972; UA001.012.004.015.00002 (Box 15)
    - Committee on Undergraduate Education (CUE): draft report - curriculum, 1972; UA001.012.004.015.00003 (Box 15)
    - Committee on Undergraduate Education (CUE): draft report - students, 1972; UA001.012.004.015.00004 (Box 15)
    - Committee on Undergraduate Education (CUE): draft report - faculty, 1972; UA001.012.004.015.00005 (Box 15)
    - Committee on Undergraduate Education (CUE): draft report - administrative structure, 1972; UA001.012.004.015.00006 (Box 15)
    - Committee on Undergraduate Education (CUE), 1972; UA001.012.004.015.00007 (Box 15)
    - Construction site crisis: daily manpower reports, 1970; UA001.012.004.015.00008 (Box 15)
    - Construction site crisis: daily manpower reports, 1969 -- 1970; UA001.012.004.015.00009 (Box 15)
    - Construction site crisis, 1969 -- 1970; UA001.012.004.015.00010 (Box 15)
    - Newsclippings: construction site crisis, 1969 -- 1970; UA001.012.004.015.00011 (Box 15)
    - Construction site crisis: general, 1967 -- 1969; UA001.012.004.016.00001 (Box 16)
      Box 1 of 3
    - Construction site crisis: general, 1969 -- 1970; UA001.012.004.016.00002 (Box 16)
      Box 2 of 3
    - Construction site crisis: general, 1969 -- 1970; UA001.012.004.016.00003 (Box 16)
      Box 3 of 3
    - Construction site crisis: BCH material, 1969; UA001.012.004.016.00004 (Box 16)
    - Construction site crisis: declaratory judgement, 1969 -- 1974; UA001.012.004.016.00005 (Box 16)
    - Construction site crisis: current backup, 1969; UA001.012.004.016.00006 (Box 16)
    - Construction site crisis: Intra-University Committee, 1969 -- 1970; UA001.012.004.016.00007 (Box 16)
    - Construction site crisis: legal documents, 1969 -- 1970; UA001.012.004.016.00008 (Box 16)
    - Construction site crisis: memos of understanding (drafts), 1969; UA001.012.004.016.00009 (Box 16)
    - Construction site crisis: overall construction, 1969; UA001.012.004.016.00010 (Box 16)
    - Construction site crisis/SDS, 1969; UA001.012.004.016.00011 (Box 16)
    - SDS/Afro-American material, 1969; UA001.012.004.016.00012 (Box 16)
    - Construction site crisis: Volpe, 1969 -- 1970; UA001.012.004.016.00013 (Box 16)
    - Economic Impact of Colleges and Universities, 1972 -- 1975; UA001.012.004.016.00014 (Box 16)
    - Faculty workload report, 1975; UA001.012.004.016.00015 (Box 16)
    - Grants, 1966 -- 1968; UA001.012.004.016.00016 (Box 16)
    - Higher Education Act - Title I, 1966 -- 1967; UA001.012.004.016.00017 (Box 16)
    - Inauguration, 1967; UA001.012.004.017.00001 (Box 17)
    - Inauguration guestbook, 1967; UA001.012.004.017.00002 (Box 17)
    - Inter-Institutional Salary Survey I, 1968 -- 1969; UA001.012.004.017.00003 (Box 17)
    - Inter-Institutional Salary Survey II, 1968 -- 1969; UA001.012.004.017.00004 (Box 17)
    - Inter-Institutional Salary Survey I, 1970 -- 1971; UA001.012.004.017.00005 (Box 17)
    - Inter-Institutional Salary Survey II, 1970 -- 1971; UA001.012.004.017.00006 (Box 17)
    - Inter-Institutional Salary Survey I, 1972 -- 1973; UA001.012.004.018.00001 (Box 18)
    - Inter-Institutional Salary Survey II, 1972 -- 1973; UA001.012.004.018.00002 (Box 18)
    - Inter-Institutional Salary Survey I, 1974 -- 1975; UA001.012.004.018.00003 (Box 18)
    - Inter-Institutional Salary Survey I & II, 1976 -- 1977; UA001.012.004.018.00004 (Box 18)
    - Internal Management Group (IMG), 1973 -- 1974; UA001.012.004.018.00005 (Box 18)
    - Internal Management Group (IMG), 1973; UA001.012.004.018.00006 (Box 18)
    - Internal Management Group (IMG), 1972 -- 1973; UA001.012.004.018.00007 (Box 18)
    - Kennedy lecture, 1972 -- 1973; UA001.012.004.018.00008 (Box 18)
    - Long-Range Planning Committee, 1968; UA001.012.004.018.00009 (Box 18)
    - Massachusetts Housing Finance Agency (MHFA), 1969 -- 1970; UA001.012.004.018.00010 (Box 18)
    - Massachusetts Housing Finance Agency (MHFA), 1969 -- 1970; UA001.012.004.018.00011 (Box 18)
    - NROTC: trustees, 1969 -- 1972; UA001.012.004.019.00001 (Box 19)
    - President's Administration Advisory Group (PAAG), 1972 -- 1974; UA001.012.004.019.00002 (Box 19)
    - President's Administration Advisory Group (PAAG), 1974 -- 1976; UA001.012.004.019.00003 (Box 19)
    - President's Administration Advisory Group (PAAG): long-range planning, 1970 -- 1971; UA001.012.004.019.00004 (Box 19)
    - President's Administration Advisory Group (PAAG): long-range planning, 1970 -- 1971; UA001.012.004.019.00005 (Box 19)
    - President's Administration Advisory Group (PAAG): long-range planning, 1970 -- 1971; UA001.012.004.019.00006 (Box 19)
    - President's Administration Advisory Group (PAAG): staff, 1973 -- 1974; UA001.012.004.019.00007 (Box 19)
    - President's Administration Advisory Group (PAAG): staff, 1975 -- 1977; UA001.012.004.019.00008 (Box 19)
    - Privacy Act (FERPA), 1974 -- 1975; UA001.012.004.020.00001 (Box 20)
    - Privacy Act (FERPA), 1974 -- 1978; UA001.012.004.020.00002 (Box 20)
    - Proposal: fundamental education, 1972; UA001.012.004.020.00003 (Box 20)
    - Public relations materials, 1966 -- 1976; UA001.012.004.020.00004 (Box 20)
    - Reports, 1968 -- 1986; UA001.012.004.020.00005 (Box 20)
    - Self-study, 1968; UA001.012.004.020.00006 (Box 20)
    - Trustee meeting: Crane School, 1967; UA001.012.004.020.00007 (Box 20)
    - Tufts in Medford, 1969; UA001.012.004.020.00008 (Box 20)
    - Tufts-New England Medical Center, Inc. (TNEMC): general, 1968 -- 1970; UA001.012.004.020.00009 (Box 20)
    - Tufts-New England Medical Center (TNEMC): affiliation agreement, 1969 -- 1970; UA001.012.004.020.00010 (Box 20)
    - Tufts-New England Medical Center (TNEMC): Columbia Point, 1966 -- 1968; UA001.012.004.020.00011 (Box 20)
    - Tufts-New England Medical Center (TNEMC): Columbia Point, 1968 -- 1970; UA001.012.004.020.00012 (Box 20)
    - Tufts-New England Medical Center (TNEMC): Columbia Point, 1970; UA001.012.004.021.00001 (Box 21)
    - Tufts-New England Medical Center (TNEMC): Columbia Point, 1971 -- 1972; UA001.012.004.021.00002 (Box 21)
    - Tufts-New England Medical Center (TNEMC): Sidney Davidson, 1957 -- 1967; UA001.012.004.021.00003 (Box 21)
    - Tufts-New England Medical Center (TNEMC): Health Action Plan, 1965 -- 1970; UA001.012.004.021.00004 (Box 21)
    - Tufts-New England Medical Center (TNEMC): Health Action Plan, 1965; UA001.012.004.021.00005 (Box 21)
    - Tufts-New England Medical Center (TNEMC): Health Action Plan, 1965 -- 1970; UA001.012.004.021.00006 (Box 21)
    - Tufts-New England Medical Center (TNEMC): Health Action Plan, 1968; UA001.012.004.021.00007 (Box 21)
    - Tufts-New England Medical Center (TNEMC): land pooling, 1969; UA001.012.004.021.00008 (Box 21)
    - Tufts-New England Medical Center (TNEMC): lease (First National Bank of Boston), 1973; UA001.012.004.021.00009 (Box 21)
    - Tufts-New England Medical Center (TNEMC): Millis Report, 1971 -- 1973; UA001.012.004.022.00001 (Box 22)
    - Tufts-New England Medical Center (TNEMC): Millis Report #2, 1972 -- 1973; UA001.012.004.022.00002 (Box 22)
    - Tufts-New England Medical Center (TNEMC): Mound Bayou (#1), 1966 -- 1969; UA001.012.004.022.00003 (Box 22)
    - Tufts-New England Medical Center (TNEMC): Mound Bayou (#2), 1969 -- 1970; UA001.012.004.022.00004 (Box 22)
    - Tufts-New England Medical Center (TNEMC): Mound Bayou, 1969 -- 1975; UA001.012.004.022.00005 (Box 22)
    - Tufts-New England Medical Center (TNEMC): Rehabilitation Institute, 1961 -- 1968; UA001.012.004.022.00006 (Box 22)
    - Tufts-New England Medical Center (TNEMC): Rehabilitation Institute, 1968; UA001.012.004.022.00007 (Box 22)
    - Tufts-New England Medical Center (TNEMC): Rehabilitation Institute, 1968 -- 1970; UA001.012.004.022.00008 (Box 22)
    - U.S. Government: general, 1974 -- 1975; UA001.012.004.023.00001 (Box 23)
    - U.S. Government: HEW, 1975; UA001.012.004.023.00002 (Box 23)
    - University Cabinet, 1967 -- 1968; UA001.012.004.023.00003 (Box 23)
    - University Steering Committee (USC): background, 1971; UA001.012.004.023.00004 (Box 23)
    - University Steering Committee (USC): members, 1971; UA001.012.004.023.00005 (Box 23)
    - University Steering Committee (USC): budget subcommittee, 1970 -- 1971; UA001.012.004.023.00006 (Box 23)
    - University Steering Committee (USC): educational programs, 1972 -- 1974; UA001.012.004.023.00007 (Box 23)
    - University Steering Committee (USC): goals subcommittee, 1972; UA001.012.004.023.00008 (Box 23)
    - University Steering Committee (USC): organization subcommittee, 1971 -- 1972; UA001.012.004.023.00009 (Box 23)
    - University Steering Committee (USC): organization subcommittee, 1970 -- 1972; UA001.012.004.023.00010 (Box 23)
    - University Steering Committee (USC) meeting, 1911 -- 1971; UA001.012.004.023.00011 (Box 23)
    - University Steering Committee (USC): meeting, 1911 -- 1971; UA001.012.004.023.00012 (Box 23)
    - University Steering Committee (USC): meeting, 1912 -- 1971; UA001.012.004.023.00013 (Box 23)
    - University Steering Committee (USC): meeting, 1912 -- 1971; UA001.012.004.023.00014 (Box 23)
    - University Steering Committee (USC): meeting, 1901 -- 1972; UA001.012.004.023.00015 (Box 23)
    - University Steering Committee (USC): meeting, 1901 -- 1972; UA001.012.004.024.00001 (Box 24)
    - University Steering Committee (USC): meeting, 1901 -- 1972; UA001.012.004.024.00002 (Box 24)
    - University Steering Committee (USC): meeting, 1902 -- 1972; UA001.012.004.024.00003 (Box 24)
    - University Steering Committee (USC): meeting, 1902 -- 1972; UA001.012.004.024.00004 (Box 24)
    - University Steering Committee (USC): meeting, 1903 -- 1972; UA001.012.004.024.00005 (Box 24)
    - University Steering Committee (USC): meeting, 1903 -- 1972; UA001.012.004.024.00006 (Box 24)
    - University Steering Committee (USC): meeting, 1905 -- 1972; UA001.012.004.024.00007 (Box 24)
    - University Steering Committee (USC): meeting, 1905 -- 1972; UA001.012.004.024.00008 (Box 24)
    - University Steering Committee (USC): meeting, 1906 -- 1972; UA001.012.004.024.00009 (Box 24)
    - University Steering Committee (USC): meeting, 1906 -- 1972; UA001.012.004.024.00010 (Box 24)
    - University Steering Committee (USC): meeting, 1907 -- 1972; UA001.012.004.024.00011 (Box 24)
    - University Steering Committee (USC): meeting, 1907 -- 1972; UA001.012.004.024.00012 (Box 24)
    - University Steering Committee (USC): meeting, 1907 -- 1972; UA001.012.004.024.00013 (Box 24)
    - University Steering Committee (USC): meeting, 1908 -- 1972; UA001.012.004.024.00014 (Box 24)
    - University Steering Committee (USC): meeting, 1909 -- 1972; UA001.012.004.024.00015 (Box 24)
    - University Steering Committee (USC): meeting, 1910 -- 1972; UA001.012.004.024.00016 (Box 24)
    - University Steering Committee (USC): meeting, 1911 -- 1972; UA001.012.004.024.00017 (Box 24)
    - University Steering Committee (USC): synopsis (draft), 1972; UA001.012.004.024.00018 (Box 24)
    - University Steering Committee (USC): budget (draft report), 1972; UA001.012.004.024.00019 (Box 24)
    - University Steering Committee (USC): conveyance (draft report), 1972; UA001.012.004.024.00020 (Box 24)
    - University Steering Committee (USC): health care (draft report), 1972; UA001.012.004.024.00021 (Box 24)
    - Univeristy Steering Committee (USC): personnel (draft report), 1972; UA001.012.004.024.00022 (Box 24)
    - University Steering Committee (USC): programs (draft report), 1972; UA001.012.004.024.00023 (Box 24)
    - University Steering Committee (USC): higher education & public funds (draft report), 1972; UA001.012.004.024.00024 (Box 24)
    - University Steering Committee (USC): calendar (draft report), 1972; UA001.012.004.024.00025 (Box 24)
    - University Steering Committee (USC): finances (draft report), 1972; UA001.012.004.024.00026 (Box 24)